<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<Episode>
  <directors>
    <item index="0">
      <photo/>
      <role/>
      <name>Takahiko Kyougoku</name>
    </item>
  </directors>
  <guest_stars/>
  <originally_available_at>2015-07-25</originally_available_at>
  <producers/>
  <rating>9.3</rating>
  <summary>The 3rd Recon Unit returns to Alnus Hill, now converted into an advanced JSDF base and Itami obtains authorization to provide shelter to the refugees, including Tuka Luna Marceau, the elf girl he saved. Meanwhile, Princess Piña Co Lada from the Empire learns more about the JSDF's exploits and decides to investigate herself. Back at Alnus, Tuka and the other refugees get used to their new lives among the Japanese soldiers, but for some reason, Tuka keeps requesting supplies not only for herself, but for another, unknown male not listed among the guests, and knowing that they can't depend on the JSDF's charity forever, she is worried about how they can provide for themselves, until Lelei points out that they can collect scales from the corpse of dragons killed by JSDF, which can fetch a good price in the local markets. Meanwhile, on the other side of the gate, the Japanese Diet requests Itami for an audience regarding the battle against the Fire Dragon, while the Chinese President also expresses his interest in the Special Region as well. However, by the time Itami is summoned, he has already left with Rory, Lelei, Tuka and the rest of the 3rd Unit to trade the scales collected at the city of Italica, where Piña and her Knights are also traveling to, in search of further info about the JSDF. </summary>
  <tags/>
  <thumbs>
    <item external="True" url="https://thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/295222/5268124.jpg" provider="com.plexapp.agents.thetvdb" media="com.plexapp.agents.thetvdb_6adde9c2700101ece6d266afbd3b55ab07cadcc3"/>
  </thumbs>
  <title>To Unknown Lands</title>
  <writers>
    <item index="0">
      <photo/>
      <role/>
      <name>Tatsuhiko Urahata</name>
    </item>
  </writers>
</Episode>
