<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<Episode>
  <directors>
    <item index="0">
      <photo/>
      <role/>
      <name>Jon Cassar</name>
    </item>
  </directors>
  <guest_stars/>
  <originally_available_at>2003-10-28</originally_available_at>
  <producers/>
  <rating>7.6</rating>
  <summary>Three years have passed since the events of Day Two. A van deposits a dead body outside the LA Health Unit. The body is infected with a deadly virus. Tony, now in charge of CTU, learns that this is a blackmail tactic to get the US government to release a drug lord, Ramon Salazar, whom Jack has just brought down, before Salazar's brother releases the virus into LA.&#13;
&#13;
Jack and his new partner, Chase Edmunds, prepare to sign a deal with Salazar at the prison.  Salazar delivers a mysterious warning to Jack before killing his lawyer.&#13;
&#13;
Palmer is alive and well, and has returned to LA for the first time since the attack three years ago. He is running for re-election and is preparing for an important debate with a rival senator. He is accompanied by his brother, who happens to be his chief of staff and his doctor, who also happens to be his girlfriend.&#13;
&#13;
A young boy, Kyle Singer, is seen examining a large, mysterious bag of white powder.  He plans to deliver it to some dealers later that day, but he is being watched by Salazar's men.&#13;
&#13;
Kim now works at CTU and has been dating Chase for three months. Kim wants to tell her father, but Jack has a mysterious health problem that may make things more complicated.&#13;
</summary>
  <tags/>
  <thumbs>
    <item external="True" url="3d228bb5d6cb418d168ee278f286bd5e" media="com.plexapp.agents.localmedia_7953ef19336e8f26f0f765580bcfd2c2c04d5e21" sort_order="1" provider="com.plexapp.agents.localmedia"/>
    <item external="True" url="https://thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/76290/189303.jpg" preview="com.plexapp.agents.thetvdb_737b2db54af2dcebefbced6bdfad7137c87b7114" provider="com.plexapp.agents.thetvdb"/>
  </thumbs>
  <title>Day 3: 1:00 P.M. - 2:00 P.M.</title>
  <writers>
    <item index="0">
      <photo/>
      <role/>
      <name>Michael Loceff</name>
    </item>
    <item index="1">
      <photo/>
      <role/>
      <name>Joel Surnow</name>
    </item>
  </writers>
</Episode>
