<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<Episode>
  <directors>
    <item index="0">
      <photo/>
      <role/>
      <name>Tomohiko Itō</name>
    </item>
  </directors>
  <guest_stars/>
  <originally_available_at>2014-07-26</originally_available_at>
  <producers/>
  <rating>7.9</rating>
  <summary>Kazuto is now logged into GGO but is baffled as to why his avatar has long hair and feminine qualities. This leads to all the male players mistaking him for a girl. Without much lead on how to reveal himself to Death Gun, Kazuto wanders until he spots a female player with blue hair, Sinon. He explains that he wants to find directions to the Governors Office to sign up for BOB, "Bullets on Bullets" an intense PvP game mode. Sinon is happy to help and directs Kazuto towards a Market to buy weaponry/armor. Being strapped for cash, Sinon offers him money but he declines and asks if there's a fast way to earn it himself. There happened to be one game; "Untouchable" a QuickDraw game where the player must dodge the NPC gun mans bullets and tag him to receive all the credits anybody has ever put in. Sinon tells him it's rigged but Kazuto believes nobody ever had the skills to defeat it, so when witnessing a player fail, Kazuto is determined to win, and his agility and training from SAO allows him to dodge with ease thus winning all the earnings. Back at the weapon shop Sinon is recommending guns but Kazuto is interested in an energy sword which he purchases immediately, although Sinon persists he at least buy a handgun to distract enemies to gain "Sword Range". Back outside Sinon realizes they only have 10 minutes to get to the Governors Office, but Kazuto spots a buggy station and rents one for a quicker get to. Sinon is impressed with Kazutos skills and enjoys the ride thus telling him to go faster!</summary>
  <tags/>
  <thumbs>
    <item external="True" url="https://thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/259640/4889023.jpg" provider="com.plexapp.agents.thetvdb" media="com.plexapp.agents.thetvdb_49f4787adae72252194d7fe6e24cd7788fcbf866"/>
  </thumbs>
  <title>GGO (Gun Gale Online)</title>
  <writers>
    <item index="0">
      <photo/>
      <role/>
      <name>Tomohiko Itō</name>
    </item>
  </writers>
</Episode>
