<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<Episode>
  <directors>
    <item index="0">
      <photo/>
      <role/>
      <name>Shinji Ishihira</name>
    </item>
  </directors>
  <guest_stars/>
  <originally_available_at>2013-12-07</originally_available_at>
  <producers/>
  <rating>9.0</rating>
  <summary>As the Conference continues Marielle reveals the secret behind preparing food with flavor followed by Michitaka's news of the collaborative invention of a steam engine. Shiroe then explains that by simply using one's own hands instead of the command menu, new things can be invented which in turn would start a supply and demand chain reaction and hence drive Akihibara's economic system. Shiroe then proposes the establishment of Human Rights laws that would ban the PKing, kidnapping and imprisonment of players and also allow them the freedom to join and leave guilds as they desire—further suggesting that these laws also apply to the People of the Land much to the conference's surprise. However, with Marielle's help, Shiroe convinces the conference of the People's importance and the dire need to coexist peacefully with them. Presented with an undeniable case, the guild masters unanimously decide on the Round Table Conference's formation and move on to inform the city and mark the occasion with a celebration. A week later, Shiroe secures a headquarters for Log Horizon and welcomes Tohya and Minori while at the same time, outside spies begin to infiltrate Akihabara. Elsewhere, the spies report back to Sergiatte of the League of Freedom Towns – Eastal district before being approached by a woman called Lady Lenessia. </summary>
  <tags/>
  <thumbs>
    <item external="True" url="https://thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/272128/4630459.jpg" provider="com.plexapp.agents.thetvdb" media="com.plexapp.agents.thetvdb_dff4b018e2228b6712dca8cf050e17f05efb3284"/>
  </thumbs>
  <title>Grab It in Your Hand</title>
  <writers>
    <item index="0">
      <photo/>
      <role/>
      <name>Mamare Touno</name>
    </item>
  </writers>
</Episode>
