<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<Episode>
  <directors>
    <item index="0">
      <photo/>
      <role/>
      <name>Shinji Ishihira</name>
    </item>
  </directors>
  <guest_stars/>
  <originally_available_at>2013-12-14</originally_available_at>
  <producers/>
  <rating>9.0</rating>
  <summary>While hunting, two People of the Land notice a strange phenomenon over the forest. Meanwhile. with Akihibara now bustling with activity, Naotsugu and Akatsuki take Tohya and Minori under their wing for training. As Shiroe also starts experimenting with his scribe subclass, Marielle starts craving to visit the beach. This gives Shiroe the idea too hold a summer training camp for new players. Afterwards, emissaries of Eastal arrive in Akihabara and invite the Round Table to a meeting and ball. Having already anticipated this, Shiroe informs Crusty that it would be a prime opportunity to learn more about the People of the Land and along with Michitaka, Henrietta, Akatsuki and Misa Takayama set off the following month. At the same time, the training camp also set off to Choushi where they end up having fun at the beach. Marielle and Minori also speak to People of the Land as part of Shiroe's suggestion that they learn as much as they can. Elsewhere, the Round Table representatives arrive at The Palace of Eternal Ice and meet with Sergiatte during the ball. As Crusty and Sergiatte begin a discussion Shiroe notes that both the adventurers and the People of the Land are weary of the other. Finally, as Princess Lenessia graces the dance with her presence, Naotsugu informs the trainees that they will head into the Forest of Lagranda dungeon for party training the next day. </summary>
  <tags/>
  <thumbs>
    <item external="True" url="https://thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/272128/4630460.jpg" provider="com.plexapp.agents.thetvdb" media="com.plexapp.agents.thetvdb_d237c152a94d1ceef33a5e0677b9dc4562977db0"/>
  </thumbs>
  <title>An Invitation from Eastal</title>
  <writers>
    <item index="0">
      <photo/>
      <role/>
      <name>Mamare Touno</name>
    </item>
  </writers>
</Episode>
