<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<Episode>
  <directors>
    <item index="0">
      <photo/>
      <role/>
      <name>Shinji Ishihira</name>
    </item>
  </directors>
  <guest_stars/>
  <originally_available_at>2013-12-28</originally_available_at>
  <producers/>
  <rating>8.5</rating>
  <summary>The Round Table Representatives find themselves with invitations to various meetings throughout the palace and they divide them amongst themselves. Shiroe will attent a dinner meeting with Count Kirino of Tsukuba and the Academic's Guild, Krusty will go to an evening party of young knights and Michitaka will attend a banquet with Lord Darte.&#13;
&#13;
Meanwhile, as Elissa warns Lenessia to be weary of the Adventurers, the latter recalls her previous meeting with Krusty where he uses  her as a convenient shield against scrutiny from the palace folk. The next day, Lenessia witnesses the sparring session with the palace knights where Krusty craftily manipulates her into accompanying him to the evening party as a reward for defeating all the knights. Elsewhere, Akatsuki eavesdrops on two noblemen at the palace and learns of a group called the Knights of Izumo, who have apparently dissapeared. Afterwards, Krusty explains to Lenessia the freedom of the Adventurers due to their resolve as opposed to her sheltered life. &#13;
&#13;
Meanwhile, Touya's Party is seen fleeing from a group of Skeletons. When they've gotten away from them, Rundelhaus Cord starts complaining that even though they are at a higher level they can't seem to defeat the Skeletons. Minori tries to speak her mind, but quickly backs down again.&#13;
&#13;
At the beach Marielle and Shoryu notice a strange phenomenon on the ocean horizon.&#13;
Back at the Ancient Palace of Eternal Ice, Lord Darte asks Michitaka to share sea faring technology with him. After Krusty and Lenessia attend the formal party, Krusty explains his interest in Lenessia by comparing her to his sister in the real world. Elsewhere, Shiroe meets with Akatsuki after his meeting with the Academic's Guild and learns of the information she gathered, when suddenly a weird phenomenon happens: everything start to vibrate and the flowers wither as the Enchanter and Assassin readied their weapons. Then suddenly a mysterious man appears, introducing himself as Ri Gan the mage from Miral Lake.</summary>
  <tags/>
  <thumbs>
    <item external="True" url="https://thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/272128/4630462.jpg" provider="com.plexapp.agents.thetvdb" media="com.plexapp.agents.thetvdb_53da94b45d7ca447822e385fad8b5f5860c519b2"/>
  </thumbs>
  <title>Shield and Freedom</title>
  <writers>
    <item index="0">
      <photo/>
      <role/>
      <name>Mamare Touno</name>
    </item>
  </writers>
</Episode>
