<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<Episode>
  <directors>
    <item index="0">
      <photo/>
      <role/>
      <name>Shinji Ishihira</name>
    </item>
  </directors>
  <guest_stars/>
  <originally_available_at>2014-02-08</originally_available_at>
  <producers/>
  <rating>8.5</rating>
  <summary>Upon arriving on the battlefield, Crusty's group engages the goblin army in battle at the Kasumi Lake. Meanwhile, at the headquarters established at the Midraunt Equestrian Park, Shiroe explains the pivotal role the town of Choushi plays in his plan to contain the goblin advancement. At the same time, a large army of Sahuagin monsters begin moving towards Choushi and the trainees persuade Marielle to let them defend the town. While watching the trainees fight, Naotsugu and Nyanta comment on their battle styles and of Minori's attempt to imitate Shiroe's Full-Control Encounter tactic. As the battle of Choushi wears on, Minori's group takes off to defend other parts of the town while Shiroe informs Marielle of the arrival of reinforcements in another hour. With the battle taking a huge toll on them, Minori's group soon finds themselves slowly overpowered against a small group of goblins and dire wolves. As Tohya's HP reaches critical levels, Minori starts losing control of the battle. However Rundelhaus suddenly charges at the last two wolves with his magical gauntlets and kills them in a suicide attack. In the aftermath, Rundelhaus' friends try in vain to heal and revive him. Already knowing the inevitable though, Isuzu tearfully explains Rundelhaus' nature as a Person of the Land—who dies permanently. Refusing to give up, Minori immediately asks Shiroe for his aid. </summary>
  <tags/>
  <thumbs>
    <item external="True" url="https://thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/272128/4630468.jpg" provider="com.plexapp.agents.thetvdb" media="com.plexapp.agents.thetvdb_a610094a05a1224af3cca36be8f554cb280e55d6"/>
  </thumbs>
  <title>Chasing After Them</title>
  <writers>
    <item index="0">
      <photo/>
      <role/>
      <name>Mamare Touno</name>
    </item>
  </writers>
</Episode>
