<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<Episode>
  <directors>
    <item index="0">
      <photo/>
      <role/>
      <name>Shinji Ishihira</name>
    </item>
  </directors>
  <guest_stars/>
  <originally_available_at>2014-02-22</originally_available_at>
  <producers/>
  <rating>8.5</rating>
  <summary>A month following the battle at Zantleaf, Eastal holds a grand ball for the adventurers for their victory against the goblin general, which Shiroe includes in his plan to eventually defeat the Goblin King in Seventh Fall. At the same time, Shiroe does his best to avoid attending the ball and learns of an event called the Demon Festival of Suzaku Gate which occurred in the west of Yamato. While walking the Palace of Eternal Ice, Shiroe surprisingly listens to a mysterious woman cryptically telling a group of children the story of how he saved Rundelhaus. Afterwards Shiroe visits Regan and learns that another adventurer in the district of Minami had also used world-class magic along with the knowledge that the Izumo Knights were involved in the Demon Festival. Back at the ball, while Crusty and Lenessia dance, the latter recalls a conversation with Sergiatte where he assigns her as the Eastal ambassador to Akihabara in order to repay the adventurers. At the same time Shiroe thanks Akatsuki for her help in their previous trials with a dance. Sometime later, Lenessia moves to Akihabara to begin her ambassadorial duties and Shiroe spreads the information of the consequences of death as a rumor to suppress panic. As things return to normal in Akihabara, Marielle proposes that they hold a festival to celebrate the autumn season. </summary>
  <tags/>
  <thumbs>
    <item external="True" url="https://thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/272128/4630470.jpg" provider="com.plexapp.agents.thetvdb" media="com.plexapp.agents.thetvdb_bfad8851bd02ccfc48e019c1626573d66e2c2357"/>
  </thumbs>
  <title>The Two of Us Shall Waltz</title>
  <writers>
    <item index="0">
      <photo/>
      <role/>
      <name>Mamare Touno</name>
    </item>
  </writers>
</Episode>
