<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<Episode>
  <directors>
    <item index="0">
      <photo/>
      <role/>
      <name>Shinji Ishihira</name>
    </item>
  </directors>
  <guest_stars/>
  <originally_available_at>2014-03-08</originally_available_at>
  <producers/>
  <rating>8.5</rating>
  <summary>The second day of the Scale Festival gets underway and the members of Log Horizon go off on their own for the day's activities. Meanwhile, Minori stops off at Karashin's busy office to procure tickets for the Twilight Banquet and offers her services while the city's inhabitants begin getting into squabbles with merchants of the People of the Land. At the same time Minori begins to use her apprentice sub-class to help Karashin account for the festival's finances. Elsewhere Nyanta peacefully kicks a rowdy Person of the Land out of a restaurant and reports the matter to Shiroe. While the Black Sword Knights and D.D.D. guilds work on maintaining order during the festival, they resolve more disputes involving the People of the Land. Issac and Crusty then discuss Shiroe's traits and agree that he works his best when for the good of others. After putting a stop to yet another rowdy Person of the Land, Shiroe finally notices the strangeness of the People's behavior and after Minori reports inconsistencies in the festival's paperwork all resulting from errors by the People, Shiroe confirms that the city may be under attack and makes haste for the Guild Building while disgruntled at his own carelessness. Meanwhile, a vessel called the New Spirit Ship led by the sinister looking Lord Malves prepares to make contact with Akihabara. </summary>
  <tags/>
  <thumbs>
    <item external="True" url="https://thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/272128/4630472.jpg" provider="com.plexapp.agents.thetvdb" media="com.plexapp.agents.thetvdb_5a7fe947a0c39a703b5be2bd5bd3f4c7824747de"/>
  </thumbs>
  <title>Student of the Mage</title>
  <writers>
    <item index="0">
      <photo/>
      <role/>
      <name>Mamare Touno</name>
    </item>
  </writers>
</Episode>
