<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<Episode>
  <directors>
    <item index="0">
      <photo/>
      <role/>
      <name>Shinji Ishihira</name>
    </item>
  </directors>
  <guest_stars/>
  <originally_available_at>2013-10-26</originally_available_at>
  <producers/>
  <rating>8.0</rating>
  <summary>Finally arriving in Susukino, Shiroe, Naotsugu and Akatsuki enter the district weary of an ambush by the Brigandia Guild. Meanwhile, as Demikas becomes alerted of their arrival, Shiroe meets up with Serara and Nyanta at a secret location, and shockingly discovers that his old friend Nyanta had been the one protecting Serara. Afterwards, Shiroe relays his plans with Naotsugu and Akatsuki and prepares to leave the district with Nyanta and Serara. After having waited patiently for them to exit the district, Shiroe, Nyanta and Serara are surrounded by the Brigandia guild and Shiroe taunts Demikas into a duel with Nyanta. As Nyanta's swashbuckler class inflicts severe status ailments on Demikas, he crudely calls in his guild members for aid however Naotsugu intercepts them with Anchor Howl. Eventually, Naotsugu and Nyanta's HP drops to dangerous levels and Shiroe has Serara heal them. With the healing having seemingly little effect, Naotsugu activates Castle of Stone and buys them enough delay time for Shiroe to ensnare Demikas in Thorn Bind Hostage, allowing Nyanta to defeat him. As Akatsuki marvels at their perfect timing and silent teamwork while taking down Demikas' remaining healers, Serara delivers the finishing blow to Demikas in defense of Shiroe, winning the battle. With their mission successful, Shiroe, Naotsugu and Nyanta summon three griffons and the party makes their way back to Akihibara. </summary>
  <tags/>
  <thumbs>
    <item external="True" url="https://thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/272128/4630453.jpg" provider="com.plexapp.agents.thetvdb" media="com.plexapp.agents.thetvdb_5fd2416705b5928f8166564fe1fd7332fb9167b2"/>
  </thumbs>
  <title>Escape</title>
  <writers>
    <item index="0">
      <photo/>
      <role/>
      <name>Mamare Touno</name>
    </item>
  </writers>
</Episode>
