<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<Episode>
  <directors>
    <item index="0">
      <photo/>
      <role/>
      <name>Shinji Ishihira</name>
    </item>
  </directors>
  <guest_stars/>
  <originally_available_at>2013-11-30</originally_available_at>
  <producers/>
  <rating>8.5</rating>
  <summary>The Round Table Conference begins as the masters of Akihibara's most influential guilds gather at the city's Guild Hall. Shiroe firstly eases that he seeks only to improve the city's living state, prompting disinterest and departure from Silver Sword's guild master—William Massachusetts. Unperturbed, Shiroe continues his explanation of the conference's formation. Elsewhere, as the Hamelin captives prepare to escape, Shiroe mentions the EXP Pot extortion campaign including Susukino's dire state with Black Sword Knights' guild master—Issac arguing the lack of laws in the world. D.D.D.'s guild master—Crusty asks of a guild's fate should they refuse the laws to which Shiroe proposes harsh sanctioning. However, Honesty's guild master—Ein along with Issac and Crusty argue of the agreement's flaw should they refuse to cooperate, with Issac even threatening war. Shiroe then plays his trump card, revealing his acquisition of the Guild Hall using the five million gold and counter blackmailing the guilds over his absolute control of their affairs. Meanwhile, as the Hamelin captives manage to escape the Hall, Minori and Tohya are unfortunately captured by Hamelin's master—Schrieder. However Shiroe's control of the Hall along with help from his friends manage to successfully blacklist all of Hamelin's members. Finally, as Shiroe makes one last pitch to the conference, Issac demands Shiroe's plan. </summary>
  <tags/>
  <thumbs>
    <item external="True" url="https://thetvdb.com/banners/episodes/272128/4630458.jpg" provider="com.plexapp.agents.thetvdb" media="com.plexapp.agents.thetvdb_499c37a370003c670c5b11439a2ae1e301f326d7"/>
  </thumbs>
  <title>Round Table Conference</title>
  <writers>
    <item index="0">
      <photo/>
      <role/>
      <name>Mamare Touno</name>
    </item>
  </writers>
</Episode>
